SKILLS

Programming Languages

C#
Php
Python

Technologies

Unity3D

MySql
Phidgets
Kinect
HTC / Oculus
Optitrack
Arduino
Ventuz Realtime
graphics
Unreal Engine

Languages

English Arabic Russian

KEY SKILLS

O QA Testing

O Agile / Scrum Methodologies

O Product Lifecycle Management

O Requirements Gathering

O Troubleshooting & Debugging

O Market & Competitors Research

CONTACT

- ♠ Dubai, United Arab Emirates
- anasbitar173@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/anasbitar-a5a875100/

ANAS BITAR PRODUCT MANAGER

PROFILE

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Currently focused on Product Management and the overall management of a product's life from conception to fruition. Bringing forth the ability to determine product specifications, production timelines, and in-depth plans for product development.

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT MANAGER

Eventagrate | 2020 - Present, Dubai

- Product manager for both internal and client projects
- Successfully launched job portal for Ministry of Communications and Information Technology, Saudia Arabia which had an attendance of more than 100,000 users in 3 days.
- Successful launch of Textron website and 360 experience. (https://experience.txtav.live/) (https://skyport.txtav.live/)
- Setup support pipeline for all internal and external projects.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Eventagrate | 2017 - 2020, Dubai

Worked with a full team building interactive applications for clients. My role was planning and building the application using Unity3D

- Worked with sensors such as phigets & Arduino
- Motion Capture (Optitrack)
- wrote custom C# scripts for the designing team that use Ventuz Realtime Graphics software (Node based)
- Developed IOS , Android & Desktop Applications
- Developed AR applications for various industries
- Developed VR Applications such as games , educational , 360 videos and others.

INTERN PROGRAMMER

IMPACT BBDO | May 2015 - June 2015, Dubai

intern programmer at impactBBDO worked on AR application for real estate were i demonstrate houses using AR using image tracking

EDUCATION

SAE INSTITUTE , BA IN GAMES PROGRAMMING SAE Institute | 2015 - 2017, Dubai